The Stupendium Youtooz figurine is available NOW!
And I'm contractually obligated to tell you about it
Within the opening minutes of a main channel video
It's only available for a limited time
And ALL the cool kids have one!
More info in the description below
Now, back to the skeletons
So, I said, 'Patella? I barely know her!’
Sans! Stop your tomfoolery!
We are here to stand guard!
Wait here and keep your eyes out for humans!
Eyes out? My eyes came out years ago!
Well, what do we got here?
They call me Sans, I'm the serif of these parts
Nah, just kiddin', I work on a grease cart
Grillin’ up hot dogs and genocidal toddlers
You can run, but I'll know if you restart
If you want a bad time, Then you're in the right place
Just look into my eye, see my funny type-face
I'm really quite a nice guy but if you pick a fight
I will hunt you all your life through time and space
Can you blame me if I feel a little hubris?
For my fame for making things a little humerus?
I can tickle your bones to the tibia toes
Well, unless you're my bro, jokes flow over his head
Sans, who's there?  You ridiculous scamp!
No one! It's just an inconspicuous lamp
If you ever meet a skeleton In towels and some Wellingtons
Just humour him and let him win And think that he's a champ
I bet you think you've never met a skeleton? Well, I bet you've Mettaton
They just had a bunch of Gooey melanin and flesh upon
But never one was In the upper echelon of clever puns
I'll make you laugh or cry Depending on the run you've set upon
We're spooky, scary Sending shivers down your spine
You best prepare For a hilariously bad time
Every human one day Ends up six feet underground
But you're heading for a grave That's buried way, way deeper down
Nyagh! A human! Call the guards!
Wait a minute, that's my job
To capture and nab you won't be hard
This maze is made with electric charge!
Wait, how did you get this far?
It took three weeks to erect this part
I genuinely didn't expect this, darn
How did you correctly guess this path?
I am Papyrus! Traps set, armed and ready
There's medals on my armour already Oh, plus some spaghetti
You're nervous! But, oh, that is good spaghetti
Where was I? I keep on forgetting
I am Papyrus! Best chef in the king's brigade
With the culinary skills To leave you flambéed
It's a shame that after You taste my blade
You won't have space For my bolognese
So, I guess you could say That they pasta-way?
Sans! Is this how you have to behave?
I'm trying to challenge This dastardly knave!
Now I've run out of bars And they just ran away!
We're spooky, scary Sending shivers down your spine
I serve spaghetti And incredibly good rhymes!
Every human one day Ends up six feet underground
But you're heading for a grave That's buried way, way deeper down
So, you took a little fall? Do you think you've got the gall To survive extermination?
Trapped deep below And all you've got to show Is your determination
There's no tu-Toriel It's Asgore-y as can be
Will the weight of your sins Leave you Snowdin?
There's no mercy
Who dares disturb me From my slumber?
Stick around This'll be a fun number
I'm truly versed in tearing All the universe asunder
I also have a specialty In unlucky spelunkers
I'm a puzzle in a bubble In the stuff of your dreams
Rupture realities and guzzle On the stuff in between
You'll be befuddled when I muscle in And muddle the scenes
Hit the shuffle and I'll tunnel Through the fuzz on your screen
You're in trouble, you see If you try and tussle with the W.D.
You'll take a tumble Then you'll crumble into rubble, debris
I bring the muscle to the scuffle Plus a couple of beams
But my blasters won't be loud enough To muffle your screams
When you're caught in the cycle Of an undying skeleton
Might as well strive to be Front of the peloton
Top of my field But out of my elements
Testing your death Would be a welcome experiment
I reign eternal So be certain that I'm well-rehearsed
Rhymes so very fine That every line feels like a multi-verse
Every parallel dimension Is at my command
But when it comes to spitting fire I've the matter in hands
We're spooky, scary Sending shivers down your spine
I'm outside of time and space But I'm afraid you're just out of time!
Every human one day Ends up six feet underground
But you're heading for a grave That's buried way, way deeper down
Nyagh! I'll get them next time, Sans! You hear me I will!
Way, way deeper down
Let me guess, You can feel it in your bones?
Eugh, I'm going! Listening to the two of you bicker Is making my skin crawl...
Metaphorically
Way, way deeper down
hey! thanks for listening... again
and thanks to all of the stupendium's incredible patrons for err...
SANS! I DID IT! I CAUGHT THE HUMAN! FOR REAL THIS TIME!
heh, no buddy, that's a youtooz figurine
SHUSH BROTHER! THEY WON'T FOOL ME WITH THEIR TINY VINYL DISGUISE!
TELL ME YOUR INSIDEOUS PLANS!
aaanyway, heh heh heh...
the stupendium's bone-afide youtooz is available now for a limited time
info below!
I'LL TEACH YOU TO BE SO MARKETABLE!!!
oh jeez...
And do be sure to like, comment, subscribe, ring the bell, check the playlist...
Ohhh you know all of this already, it's the same in every universe...
SANS, GOOD NEWS! THE FIGURINE AND I ARE GOING ON A DATE
I HOPE THEY LIKE SPAGHETTI! NYAGH!!!